A Guide to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records FA025
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, 1875, 1878, 1916-2001 1969-2001; 2; 28 Cubic Feet
  - Administration, 1942, 1977, 1980-1998; 1
    - Grants Committee and Board of Trustees, 1994-1998; 7
      - Grants Committee and Board of Trustees Meetings I, October 7, 1998 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
        Albion College American Composers Forum Cedar Crest College Claremont University Center Johns Hopkins University Illinois Wesleyan University National Trust for Historic Preservation in the United States New Jersey Symphony Orchestra New York University Northeastern University Spanish Theatre Repertory Company Ltd.
      - Grants Committee and Board of Trustees Meetings II, October 7, 1998 (Reel 9, Frame 195)
    - Investment Committee, 1988-1994; 8
      The financial management of the Foundation's investment base is documented in this subseries.
      - Series 1.8 - Administration - Investment Committee, 1988-1994 (Reel 9, Frame 385)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1989 (Reel 9, Frame 386)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1990 (Reel 9, Frame 450)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1991 (Reel 9, Frame 620)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1992 (Reel 9, Frame 789)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence - Part I, 1993 (Reel 9, Frame 981)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence - Part II, 1993 (Reel 9, Frame 1102)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1994 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
      - Investment Committee Meetings - Correspondence, 1995 (Reel 10, Frame 40)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, February 14, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 55)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, May 23, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 64)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, July 25, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 77)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, November 15, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 87)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, January 18, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 95)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, April 27, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 99)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, August 14, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 109)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, October 31, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 125)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, January 9, 1991 (Reel 10, Frame 134)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, May 14, 1991 (Reel 10, Frame 141)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, November 12, 1991 (Reel 10, Frame 165)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, April 8, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 175)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, June 4, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 182)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, July 20, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 205)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, September 9, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 211)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, November 18, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 217)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, December 29, 1992 (Reel 10, Frame 221)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, March 16, 1993 (Reel 10, Frame 229)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, June 1, 1993 (Reel 10, Frame 235)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, September 16, 1993 (Reel 10, Frame 242)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, December 6, 1993 (Reel 10, Frame 246)
      - Investment Committee Meetings, March 24, 1994 (Reel 10, Frame 253)
      - Proxy Voting Procedures, 1988, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 265)
    - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1987-1998; 9
      The Scientific Advisory Committee was composed of six physician-scientists whose primary responsibility was to review the applications for the Scholarships in Medical Science and to select the awardees.
      Series 1.9 is arranged chronologically.
      - Series 1.9 - Administration - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1987-1998 (Reel 10, Frame 337)
      - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1987-1990 (Reel 10, Frame 338)
      - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1991-1994 (Reel 10, Frame 529)
      - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1995-1998 (Reel 10, Frame 671)
  - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Reports, 1940-1999; 2
    Reports documenting Foundation activities were published in five-year increments from 1975-1999. These composite Anniversary Reports were at the time deemed satisfactory for organizational reporting requirements according to the Tax Reform Act of 1969. The Foundation distributed its first report in 1975.
    The anniversary reports, considered out-of-date by the time of publication, were therefore thought to be of limited value to recipients or even misleading. In 1993, a Biennial Report was produced covering the years 1991-1992. After this time, the Trustees determined that the Foundation should produce a report annually. The annual publication of reports continued from 1993 until 1998. The publication of a final "Retrospective" covered the time span from the inception of the Foundation's operations in 1940 to the terminus of the Foundation's activities as an independent philanthropy in 1999.
    The Trustees' goal was to provide these reports as a tool for potential grantees to determine the applicability of established Foundation programs to satisfy their grant needs. Published program guidelines brochures were considered supplementary to these reports, as were several additional published reports including "Adventurous Teachers, Excellent Schools" by Thomas James and "A Review of the Library Automation Program" by Ellen Arrick. These reports are also available in bound format in the Archive Center's library collection.
    Series 2 is arranged chronologically.
    Annual reports
    - Series 2 - Annual Reports, 1940-1999 (Reel 10, Frame 765)
    - 35th Anniversary Report, 1940-1975 (Reel 10, Frame 766)
    - 40th Anniversary Report, 1940-1980 (Reel 10, Frame 788)
    - 45th Anniversary Report, 1940-1985 (Reel 10, Frame 807)
    - 50th Anniversary Report, 1940-1990 (Reel 10, Frame 825)
    - Retrospective, 1940-1999 (Reel 10, Frame 846)
    - Biennial Report, 1991-1992 (Reel 10, Frame 892)
    - Annual Report, 1993 (Reel 10, Frame 907)
    - Annual Report, 1994 (Reel 10, Frame 929)
    - Annual Report, 1995 (Reel 10, Frame 957)
    - Annual Report, 1996 (Reel 10, Frame 984)
    - Annual Report, 1997 (Reel 10, Frame 1010)
    - Annual Report, 1998 (Reel 10, Frame 1048)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1993 (Box REF 060 CHA 1993)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1994 (Box REF 060 CHA 1994)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1995 (Box REF 060 CHA 1995)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1996 (Box REF 060 CHA 1996)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1997, 1 (Box REF 060 CHA 1997)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation Annual Report 1998 (Box REF 060 CHA 1998)
  - Grants, 1964, 1969-2001; 3
    The Charles E. Culpeper Foundation focused upon grant programs in several broad categories which included the Administration of Justice, Arts and Culture, Education, and Health Care. Additional programs within each area determined the nature of the awards offered to applicants. The Foundation issued grants only within these four broad designations and their subdivisions. Grants that did not meet these criteria were denied.
    Series 2 is arranged in 7 subseries:
    Subseries 1 - Administration of Justice Grants
    Subseries 2 - Arts and Culture Grants
    Subseries 3 - Discretionary Grants
    Subseries 4 - Education Grants
    Subseries 5 - General Grants
    Subseries 6 - Grant Lists
    Subseries 7 - Health and Medical Program Grants
    - Administration of Justice Grants, 1974-1996; 1
      The Foundation issued grants in the Administration of Justice program for over twenty years. Prior to 1980, the Foundation devoted approximately five percent of its grant program to support programs in this area. Support focused upon alternate dispute resolution, education of judges, judicial-congressional relations, educating the public regarding the operation of the judicial system, and addressing problems in the administration of criminal justice. One of the major recipients of Foundation grants in this category was the Governance Institute of Washington, D.C. One hallmark project funded was entitled "Challenges to the Legal Profession," which sought to develop a procedure to encourage a more humanistic approach in the profession, as well as to develop a consensus about lawyers' ethical obligations and responsibilities to society.
      During the 1990s, the objectives of this program shifted to focus more specifically upon problems affecting the general public in the workings of the criminal justice system. Programs addressed the need for an informed citizenry to participate in effecting changes in law enforcement, and focused, particularly, on how to maximize results in the prevention and reduction of violent crime. The Administration of Justice grants program was terminated in 1997.
      Series 3.1 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
      - Series 3.1 - Grants - Administration of Justice Grants, 1974-1996 (Reel 10, Frame 1086)
      - Administrative Conference of the United States, 1989-1990, 1992-1993 (Reel 10, Frame 1087)
      - American Bar Association, 1976-1977 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
      - American Bar Association, 1978 (Reel 11, Frame 166)
      - American Bar Association, 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 248)
      - American Bar Association, 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 422)
      - American Bar Association, 1981-1983 (Reel 11, Frame 614)
      - American Bar Association, 1984-1986 (Reel 11, Frame 742)
      - American Bar Association, 1987-1989 (Reel 11, Frame 859)
      - American Bar Foundation, 1991-1993 (Reel 11, Frame 1071)
      - American Enterprise Institute, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1989 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
      - American Judicature Society, 1978-1982, 1984-1986 (Reel 12, Frame 178)
      - The Association of the Bar of the City of New York Fund, Inc., 1984-1985, 1987-1990 (Reel 12, Frame 308)
      - The Association of the Bar of the City of New York Fund, Inc., 1991-1994, 1996 (Reel 12, Frame 406)
      - California Judges Association and the Edmund G. "Pat" Brown Institute of Public Affairs of California State University I, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 552)
      - California Judges Association and the Edmund G. "Pat" Brown Institute of Public Affairs of California State University II, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 730)
      - California Judges Association and the Edmund G. "Pat" Brown Institute of Public Affairs of California State University III, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 936)
      - California Judges Association and the Edmund G. "Pat" Brown Institute of Public Affairs of California State University, 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      - Center for Judicial Studies, 1987, 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 193)
      - Center for Public Resources, 1979-1986 (Reel 13, Frame 210)
      - Center for Public Resources, 1988-1991 (Reel 13, Frame 401)
      - Center for Public Resources, 1996 (Reel 13, Frame 602)
      - Connecticut Bar Foundation, 1984-1986 (Reel 13, Frame 709)
      - Court Appointed Special Advocate Program, 1988-1990 (Reel 13, Frame 834)
      - Criminal Justice Legal Foundation, 1990-1991 (Reel 13, Frame 858)
      - First Department Assigned Council Corporation, Supreme Court of the State of New York, 1988 (Reel 13, Frame 933)
      - Harvard University, 1977, 1980-1992 (Reel 13, Frame 951)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, 1983-1986 (Reel 13, Frame 1157)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, 1987-1988 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, 1989-1992 (Reel 14, Frame 169)
      - National Center for Citizen Participation in the Administration of Justice, 1988-1990 (Reel 14, Frame 352)
      - National Center for State Courts, 1974-1977 (Reel 14, Frame 416)
      - National Center for State Courts, 1978-1979 (Reel 14, Frame 521)
      - National Center for State Courts, 1980-1984, 1986-1987 (Reel 14, Frame 713)
      - National College of District Attorneys, 1988-1993 (Reel 14, Frame 821)
      - National College of the State Judiciary, 1977-1980 (Reel 14, Frame 1017)
      - National Legal Center for the Public Interest, 1979-1994 (Reel 14, Frame 1143)
      - National Judicial College, 1978-1984 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
      - National Judicial College, 1985-1990, 1992 (Reel 15, Frame 97)
      - San Antonio Community Law Center, 1988-1994 (Reel 15, Frame 190)
      - Sta-Fed ADR, Inc., 1992-1994 (Reel 15, Frame 368)
        Alternative Dispute Resolution.
      - Sta-Fed ADR, Inc., 1995-1996 (Reel 15, Frame 455)
      - Vera Institute of Justice, 1980-1981, 1984 (Reel 15, Frame 570)
      - Veterans Administration Medical Center, 1984-1986 (Reel 15, Frame 573)
      - Volunteers of Legal Service, Inc., 1986-1991 (Reel 15, Frame 622)
      - Williamette University, 1984-1985 (Reel 15, Frame 670)
    - Arts and Culture Grants, 1969, 1972, 1974-2001; 2
      The Foundation supported programs within the realm of Arts and Culture in three areas: Exploration Grants, to allow participating organizations to introduce an initiative; Program Grants, to support new or existing projects which focused on providing access to arts and culture programs; and Endowments in Arts and Culture, awarded to those organizations who had already demonstrated a commitment to educating the public in their area of endeavor.
      Series 3.2 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
      - Series 3.2 - Grants - Arts and Culture Grants, 1969, 1972, 1974-2001, 1969-2001 (Reel 15, Frame 726)
      - Findings and Recommendations of the Arts and Culture Program of the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, December 1996 (Reel 15, Frame 727)
      - Program Evaluation Proposals, 1978, 1995 (Reel 15, Frame 824)
      - Program Evaluation Proposals, 1996 (Reel 15, Frame 1063)
      - The Acting Company, 1991-1994 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
      - Addison Gallery of American Art, 1981-1984 (Reel 16, Frame 200)
      - Affiliate Artists, Inc., 1991-1992 (Reel 16, Frame 249)
      - American Antiquarian Society, 1988-1993 (Reel 16, Frame 368)
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1992-1994 (Reel 16, Frame 463)
      - American Museum of Natural History, 1981-1985 (Reel 16, Frame 483)
      - American Philosophical Society, 1982-1985, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 522)
      - American School of Classical Studies, 1981-1987 (Reel 16, Frame 585)
      - Anchorage Museum of History and Art, 1996 (Reel 16, Frame 713)
      - The Association of American Cultures, 1990 (Reel 16, Frame 718)
      - Bach Area Group Association, Inc., 1984-1985 (Reel 16, Frame 757)
      - Bargemusic, Ltd., 1990, 1992-1994 (Reel 16, Frame 760)
      - Brandy Station Foundation, 1988-1989 (Reel 16, Frame 786)
      - Brandy Station Foundation, 1990 (Reel 16, Frame 924)
      - Brandy Station Foundation, 1991 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
      - Brandy Station Foundation, 1992-1996 (Reel 17, Frame 134)
      - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, 1984-1990, 1995 (Reel 17, Frame 242)
      - The Brooklyn Museum, 1988-1990 (Reel 17, Frame 359)
      - The Cape Code Museum of Natural History, Inc., 1984 (Reel 17, Frame 414)
      - Caramoor Center for Music and the Arts, Inc., 1985-1988, 1992 (Reel 17, Frame 417)
      - Care Selve Center for Blind Musicians, Inc., 1987-1989 (Reel 17, Frame 455)
      - Cedar Rapids Museum of Art, 1985 (Reel 17, Frame 473)
      - Children's Museum of Indianapolis, 1985, 1987-1990 (Reel 17, Frame 476)
      - Colden Center for the Performing Arts, 1987-1988 (Reel 17, Frame 627)
      - Connecticut Historical Society, 1990-1991, 1993-1994 (Reel 17, Frame 647)
      - Connecticut Trust for Historic Preservation, 1978-1982 (Reel 17, Frame 684)
      - Connecticut Trust for Historic Preservation, 1983-1991 (Reel 17, Frame 864)
      - Council for the Arts in Westchester, 1986-1990 (Reel 17, Frame 971)
      - Dance Notation Bureau, 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 1026)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1981-1989 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1990-1996 (Reel 18, Frame 197)
      - Deer Valley Chamber Music Society, 1988 (Reel 18, Frame 444)
      - Denver Center for the Performing Arts, 1988-1990 (Reel 18, Frame 462)
      - Dona Ana Arts Council, Inc., 1982-1988 (Reel 18, Frame 485)
      - Dublin Historical Society, 1991 (Reel 18, Frame 630)
      - East Lyme Library Building Fund, 1989 (Reel 18, Frame 632)
      - The Fairfield Chamber Orchestra, 1984 (Reel 18, Frame 634)
      - Festival of Music, 1991-1995 (Reel 18, Frame 636)
      - Friends of Franklin, 1989-1990 (Reel 18, Frame 804)
      - Gloucester Museum School, 1977-1984 (Reel 18, Frame 826)
      - Institute for Contemporary Art, 1989 (Reel 18, Frame 845)
      - Jupiter Symphony, 1982-1988 (Reel 18, Frame 877)
      - The Lockwood-Mathews Mansion Museum, 1972, 1974, 1977, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 913)
      - Lyme Academy of Fine Arts, 1994 (Reel 18, Frame 928)
      - Lyric Opera of Chicago, 1987, 1992-1995 (Reel 18, Frame 931)
      - The MacDuffie School, 1983-1984 (Reel 18, Frame 1158)
      - The Mannes College of Music, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 1186)
      - Marlboro School of Music, 1982, 1985-1987, 1989-1991 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
      - Marlboro School of Music, 1992-1994 (Reel 19, Frame 147)
      - Martha Graham School of Contemporary Dance, Inc., 1990-1994 (Reel 19, Frame 378)
      - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1985-1988 (Reel 19, Frame 432)
      - Merkin Concert Hall, 1984-1986 (Reel 19, Frame 469)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1981, 1984-1986, 1989-1990, 1993 (Reel 19, Frame 488)
      - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1975-1979 (Reel 19, Frame 548)
      - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1980-1985 (Reel 19, Frame 636)
      - Mount Vernon's Ladies Association of the Union, 1983, 1992 (Reel 19, Frame 726)
      - Musica Sacra of New York, 1978-1980 (Reel 19, Frame 729)
      - Musica Sacra of New York, 1981-1982, 1984-1985, 1987-1990 (Reel 19, Frame 824)
      - National Chorale Foundation, 1986-1987 (Reel 19, Frame 937)
      - The National Theatre of the Deaf, Inc., 1988-1990 (Reel 19, Frame 957)
      - National Theatre Workshop of the Handicapped, 1986-1991 (Reel 19, Frame 993)
      - New York Youth Symphony, 1985 (Reel 19, Frame 1086)
      - New York Zoological Society, 1969, 1978-1981, 1990-1992, 1997 (Reel 19, Frame 1089)
      - 92nd Street Young Men's and Young Women's Hebrew Association (YM-YWHA), 1980-1985 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
      - North Carolina Symphony, 1991-1994 (Reel 20, Frame 135)
      - Old Sturbridge Village, 1986-1989 (Reel 20, Frame 237)
      - 100th Street Concerts Association, Inc., 1993-1994 (Reel 20, Frame 262)
      - Opera Memphis, 1990-1991 (Reel 20, Frame 267)
      - Opera/Mucis Theatre Institute of New Jersey, 1987-1989 (Reel 20, Frame 285)
      - Oregon Shakespearean Festival, 1988-1989 (Reel 20, Frame 316)
      - Original Ballets Foundation, Inc., 1992-1996, 1998 (Reel 20, Frame 328)
      - Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, 1989 (Reel 20, Frame 433)
      - Pennsylvania Ballet, 1991-1992 (Reel 20, Frame 464)
      - Pennsylvania Ballet, 1993 (Reel 20, Frame 537)
      - Portland School of Art, 1989-1990, 1993, 1995, 1997, 2000 (Reel 20, Frame 645)
      - Ravinia Festival, 1990-1993 (Reel 20, Frame 687)
      - Tiny Mythic Theatre Company, 1992 (Reel 20, Frame 790)
      - Rhode Island Historical Society (John Brown House), 1986-1987 (Reel 20, Frame 792)
      - The School of American Ballet, 1979-1983; 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 810)
      - Seattle Opera Association, 1983-1987 (Reel 20, Frame 914)
      - Seattle Opera Association, 1989-1991 (Reel 20, Frame 1068)
      - Seattle Opera Association, 1992-1993, 1996-2001 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
      - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1984-1986, 1989 (Reel 21, Frame 238)
      - Snug Harbor Cultural Center, 1986-1992 (Reel 21, Frame 265)
      - Stamford Center for the Arts, 1981, 1983-1985 (Reel 21, Frame 352)
      - Stamford Center for the Arts, 1986-1994 (Reel 21, Frame 525)
      - Stamford Historical Society, Inc., 1988-1991 (Reel 21, Frame 673)
      - Stamford Museum and Nature Center, 1979-1990 (Reel 21, Frame 693)
      - Symphony Space, 1985-1987 (Reel 21, Frame 716)
      - Third Street Music School Settlement, 1982-1990 (Reel 21, Frame 734)
      - Valentine Museum, 1977-1979, 1981-1983, 1985-1986 (Reel 21, Frame 854)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation, 1978-1981 (Reel 21, Frame 900)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation, 1982-1988 (Reel 21, Frame 1026)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Inside Gorbachev's USSR with Hedrick Smith, 1989-April 1990 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Inside Gorbachev's USSR with Hedrick Smith, May-December 1990, 1996 (Reel 22, Frame 175)
      - WNET Thirteen, 1977-1986, 1998 (Reel 22, Frame 361)
      - West End Symphony, Inc., 1985 (Reel 22, Frame 499)
      - Westchester Symphony Orchestra, 1988-1989 (Reel 22, Frame 504)
      - Wildlife of the American West - National Wildlife Art Museum, 1993 (Reel 22, Frame 531)
      - Wildlife of the American West - National Wildlife Art Museum, 1994-1996 (Reel 22, Frame 742)
      - Winterthur Museum and Gardens, 1991-1996 (Reel 22, Frame 905)
      - The Wolf Trap Foundation for the Performing Arts, 1986-1988 (Reel 22, Frame 965)
      - Women's Prison Association and Home, 1992 (Reel 22, Frame 987)
      - Worcester Art Museum, 1987-1995, 1997-1998 (Reel 22, Frame 1007)
      - Yale Institute of Sacred Music, Worship and the Arts, 1978, 1986-1989, 1991 (Reel 22, Frame 1091)
      - Young Audiences, 1980-1984 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
      - Young Audiences, 1985-1991 (Reel 23, Frame 209)
      - Young Audiences, 1993-1995 (Reel 23, Frame 561)
    - Discretionary Grants, 1974, 1977-1998; 3
      Discretionary grants were issued to organizations deemed worthy of need by an individual Board member. Allotments for this purpose were designated by a Board of Trustees decision.
      Series 3.3 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
      - Series 3.3 - Grants - Discretionary Grants, 1974, 1977-1998, 1974-1998 (Reel 23, Frame 723)
      - American Friends Service Committee, 1987 (Reel 23, Frame 724)
      - Associates of Lincoln Center, 1983-1985 (Reel 23, Frame 729)
      - Assumption and All Saints School, 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 733)
      - Benedictine Grange, 1981-1985 (Reel 23, Frame 737)
      - Boniface Center, 1989 (Reel 23, Frame 739)
      - Bridgeville Public Library, 1981-1982 (Reel 23, Frame 741)
      - The Capuchin Fathers, 1988-1989 (Reel 23, Frame 744)
      - Catholic Charities Diocese of Palm Beach, Inc., 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 749)
      - Choate Rosemary Hall Foundation, Inc., 1988-1993 (Reel 23, Frame 763)
      - Christian Life Communities, 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 804)
      - Church of the Holy Famly, 1977-1982, 1985, 1987,1989 (Reel 23, Frame 808)
      - Church of St. Ignatius Loyola, 1980-1989 (Reel 23, Frame 818)
      - Church of St. Paul, 1986-1990 (Reel 23, Frame 823)
      - Coat of Many Colors, Inc., 1992 (Reel 23, Frame 833)
      - Columbus House, 1987, 1989-1990 (Reel 23, Frame 835)
      - Community Soup Kitchen, 1988, 1991 (Reel 23, Frame 842)
      - Darien Community Association, Inc. - Program for the Blind, 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 846)
      - Deborah Hospital Foundation, 1990-1992 (Reel 23, Frame 848)
      - Denison University, 1984-1987, 1987-1990 (Reel 23, Frame 898)
      - The Dwelling Place, 1980-1982, 1987-1988 (Reel 23, Frame 1123)
      - Fairview United Presbyterian Church, 1978, 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 1130)
      - Family Health Foundation of America, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 1134)
      - The First Presbyterian Church in the City of New York, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1989 (Reel 23, Frame 1136)
      - First United Methodist Church (Holly Burn Fund), 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
      - Fitkin Hospital, Jersey Shore Medical Center, 1974 (Reel 24, Frame 3)
      - The Five Towns Foundation, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 5)